CODE-R なるほど
Code-R...
I see. You've given me
an abnormal level...
活動電位とニューロフィラメントが
異常数値でした
of active electrical potential
and neurofilaments.
理解は幸せ
It's such a pleasure to understand!
私を実験体にして
再現しようとしましたですね
You experimented on me in
order to recreate it, didn't you?
この病を
This disease of hers...
CODE-Rは病人ではない
Code-R isn't an invalid!
ともかく おとなしくしてくれんか
貴公の脳細胞はウイルスの動脈輪から…
In any case,
won't you please calm down?
Your brain cells were severed
from the Circle of Willis, so...
言い訳 無駄！
Spare me your excuses!
あなたを本国送りにした恨み
こんな形で頂きました
You made me like this because you hated
me for sending you back to the homeland!
分かった　あとで いくらでも
話は聞くから 本国に戻ろう
All right, I promise, I'll listen to anything you have
to say, but let's get back to the homeland first!
こんな状態では
会話すら まともにできん
We can't have a proper
conversation in this situation!
Hear me, Britannia!
聞くが良い！　ブリタニアよ！
おおっ！
我が名はゼロ！
My name is Zero!
ゼロ…
Zero!
力ある者に対する反逆者である
０時まで待とう
A rebel against those with power!
We will wait until midnight.
You have until then to surrender to me.
う…
降伏し 我が軍門に下れ！
租界全域で？
The entire settlement?
はい
Yes, sir. He's on
all the communication channels.
通信チャンネルが…
では外部への連絡手段は？
Then there's no way
to contact the outside!
Hmpf... Use this chance to
confirm the enemy's formation.
今のうちに敵軍の配置を確認せよ
イエス ユア・ハイネス
Yes, Your Highness.
ユーフェミアの仇…
I will have vengeance for Euphemia,
and I'll take it right here and now, Zero!
ここで討たせてもらうぞ ゼロ
正々堂々と正面からな
Fair, open, and face to face!
これは最終通告だ
This is your final warning!
０時まで待つ　我が軍門に下れ
We will wait until midnight.
You have until then to surrender!
ん… 軍門に下れ ０時に租界を…
Surrender! At midnight,
surrender the settlement...
お… おい　何やってるんだ
H- Hey! What are you doing?!
Stop it! If you do that!
やめろ！　こんな事をしたら…
邪魔をしないで くれないか？
Would you please not interfere?
ふざけてる場合か　今すぐやめないと…
This is no time to be kidding around!
If you don't stop...
あっ！
爆撃の準備は？
Are you ready to commence bombing?
時間合わせでいけます
Timed on target.
よし！
Good. Take position to fire!
撃ち方 用意！
コーネリア
Cornelia. Insisting on a frontal
attack will be your undoing.
正面からの戦いにとらわれた
お前の負けだ
何っ？
What?!
あちゃっ
地震？
An earthquake?!
は…
地震対策の為の階層構造
A layered structure,
built to be earthquake resistant.
しかし フロアパーツを
一斉にパージすれば
But if you purge all of the floor sections
simultaneously, there's nothing more fragile!
これほど脆い物はない
黒の騎士団を迎え撃つ為
外縁に布陣したのが仇になったな
By gathering on the city's perimeter to engage
the Black Knights, you sealed your fate!
I'm not beaten yet!
私は まだ！
ゼロ… やっぱお前すげえよ
Zero... You really are amazing!
うわあ！　租界を全部壊したんですか？
Is the entire settlement collapsing?
外縁部のみと聞いております
後々 必要とされる施設もありますから
I heard it was just the outer perimeter.
There are facilities in it we'll need later.
しかし…
ゼロは地下協力員をどうやって？
Still, how did Zero's underground
collaborators do this?
やはりヴィレッタやジェレミアの
推測は正しかったという事か？
Villetta and Jeremiah's theories
must have been true.
ふっ ならば素晴らしい
そう 世界の前には人は駒でしかない
Then this is magnificent!
Yes... Before the world,
people are just pawns!
痛む場所は 誰にも云わない
itamu basho darenimo iwanai
I don't tell anyone where I hurt
急ぐ心が 隠した夢を
isogu kokoro ga kakushita yume wo
I stare at the dreams hidden by my hurried heart
壊れそうな 瞳で見つめる
kowaresouna hitomi de mitsumeru
With fragile eyes
押さえきれない チカラだけ
osaekirenai chikara dake
Only my unchecked power
離さずに 翔び立つ
hanasazu ni tobitatsu
Flies out without separating from me
巡り逢いが 動き出す
meguriai ga ugokidasu
Chance encounters hasten...
運命を早めて
unmei wo hayamete
Destiny as it starts to move
せめて君が駆け抜ける
semete kimi ga kakenukeru
At least tell me the instant...
一瞬を 教えて
isshun wo oshiete
When you come running through
THE COLLAPSING STAGE
ふっ ははははははっ
これでいい
This will do. Once we broadcast images
of the government bureau falling to us...
あとは政庁陥落の映像と共に
独立宣言を全世界に向けて発信すれば
and our declaration of
independence to the world,
嫌でも あの男が出てくる
then he'll have to face me,
whether he likes it or not!
And if I can get him... Get the Britannian
emperor to meet me face to face,
奴に… ブリタニア皇帝に
直接 会う事ができれば
全てのカードは 我が手に落ちる
then all the cards will fall into my hands!
敵の航空戦力はどうなった？
How does the enemy's
air power look?
Our allied groups are concentrating
on hitting them in each sector.
各地域の協力組織も
優先して叩いています
残るは イズ諸島とサド
アワジあたりかと
The rest are around the Izu
Archipelago, Sado, and Awaji.
よし　ならば今のうちだ
All right, then now's our chance!
Attack!
突撃！
三番隊は報道機関　六番隊は公安部
特務隊は滑走空域を押さえろ
Squad 3, take the media sector.
Squad 6, take the harbor!
Special forces squad,
suppress the lower levels!
それ以外は正面から押し出せ
敵軍 残存勢力の情報を収集
Everyone aside from that,
push in from the front!
Gather data on all
remaining enemy forces!
引け！　引けー！
Retreat! Retreat!
All forces, fall back to the
Britannian government bureau!
全軍ブリタニア政庁まで後退せよ！
イエス ユア・ハイネス！
Yes, Your Highness!
どうした？　操縦が困難ならば
コックピットブロックだけでも
What's wrong? If you're having trouble controlling
it, we could swap out the cockpit block.
コ… コーネリア様
私になど構わず 先に政庁へ
P- Princess Cornelia, forget
about me and get to the bureau!
コーネリアを確認した　囲め！
Cornelia's been found!
Surround her!
えいっ！
えっ
覚悟！
Prepare yourself!
Tohdoh! You ghost!
藤堂！　この亡霊が！
Princess! Leave this to me!
姫様！　ここは私にお任せを！
ギルフォード！
Guilford!
The one from Narita!
ナリタにいた あいつか
Use this chance
to get to the bureau!
今のうちに政庁へ
この私に
部下をおいて逃げよと言うのか！
You expect me to leave
my men and run away?!
姫様は 生きねば なりません！
ユーフェミア様の為にも！
Your Highness, you must live!
For Princess Euphemia's sake, too!
う…
Yes! Because I am a knight
chosen by you to defend you!
そう 私は姫様に選ばれた
姫様を守る為の騎士！
うっ ランスロットと同じあれか
The same as the Lancelot's!
ならばここは… 私こそが！
And so I must be the one
who fights here!
分かった　命令だ　生きて帰れよ
我が騎士ギルフォード
Very well. Then I order you:
Come back to me alive,
Guilford, my knight.
イエス ユア・ハイネス！
Yes, Your Highness!
零番隊は特務隊と共に
学園地区を優先して押さえろ
The special forces squad and Zero Squad
will give priority to the school grounds.
その中の１つに 司令部をおく
We'll set up our command center
in one of the buildings.
えっ！　学園地区に？
What? On the school grounds?
扇 お前もそこで配置につけ
Ohgi, you stand by
there as well. Ohgi!
扇！
あっ ああ　分かった
R- Right. Understood.
あっ！
行くつもりだね？　トウキョウ租界に
でも…
You're planning to go to the
Tokyo settlement, aren't you?
However... Congratulations!
おめでとう！
く…
この特派は研究開発が目的でね
やるべき事は全て終わったんだ
A.S.E.E.C. exists for research
and development.
Our duties here are at an end.
総督から出撃命令も出ていない
だから ここを出ると命令違反だよお？
And the viceroy hasn't ordered
us to go out there, either.
So, leaving here will be
a violation of orders, right?
スザク君　気持ちは分かるけど…
Suzaku, I know how you feel, but...
ダメだよおーん
No, you don't!
あっ！
あ…
あっ
トウキョウには ゼロがいるんだ！
俺は 俺の手でゼロを倒す！
Zero's in Tokyo! I'm going to
finish him with my own hands!
ううう…
I won't let you stop me!
I'm doing this!
邪魔はさせない！　俺がやるんだ！
Tohdoh!
藤堂さん
中佐 追撃しますか？
Lt. Colonel, should we pursue?
他の部隊はどうなった？
Where are the other units?
側面から上昇中で… ん？
They're climbing up from the side... Hm?!
あっ
The Glaston Knights?
グラストンナイツか？
ギルフォード卿
この先に陣を敷きました
Lord Guilford, we're holding a position
just ahead of here. Please head back!
お戻り下さい
Thanks, I appreciate it!
すまない　礼を言う
それには及びません
私達は 元々ダールトン将軍の配下です
Think nothing of it, sir.
We were all originally
Gen. Darlton's subordinates.
将軍の生死が分からずとも
コーネリア総督に仕える事が最優先です
We still don't know if
the general's alive or dead,
but being of service to Viceroy
Cornelia comes before all else!
Do you know the situation?
状況は分かるか？
正面の敵は陽動かと
しかし… ここを潰せば あとは民兵
The enemies attacking
from the front are a diversion.
But if we beat them here,
the rest we deal with are just militia forces.
つまり…
In other words... rabble.
雑魚です
ディートハルト 航空戦力は片付いた
Diethard! Their air power
has been taken care of!
Ｇ－１は神楽耶に任せろ
お前は予定地へ移動しろ
Leave G1 to Kaguya.
Move to your assigned location!
分かりました
Understood.
吉田は 雷光の準備
Yoshida, prepare the Raikou!
ああ
Right!
玉城 ラクシャータは？
Tamaki, where's Rakshata?
移動中だ
On the move!
Kallen, move to back them up!
カレンは バックアップに回れ
はい
Right!
Tohdoh, if the target appears...
藤堂 対象が現れたら
分かっている
Understood.
よし
All right...
Ohgi, what's the collaborator's name?
扇 協力者の名は？
あっ ああ
R- Right,
I have it as Sayoko Shinozaki.
篠崎咲世子といって…
あ…
BRITANNIAN HOMELAND - COURT CONFERENCE ROOM
ヒロシマ租界 交信途絶
サッポロ租界でも 暴動が発生した模様
Contact lost with Hiroshima settlement!
Uprisings have apparently broken out
in the Sapporo settlement as well!
東シナ海に 中華連邦軍艦隊の
集結を確認しました
We confirm that Chinese Federation naval
forces are massing in the East China Sea!
The Chinese Federation, too?!
中華連邦まで
んっ こんな時に陛下がいないなんて…
That's all we need,
with His Majesty still not here!
また あそこか…
He's gone there, again?
Prince Odysseus,
we're ready to deploy troops.
オデュッセウス殿下
派兵の準備はできております
指揮官の任命を
Please assign the commanders.
Let's not be too hasty.
急に言われてもねえ
ユーフェミアの件は明らかな失態だし
処理を間違うと全てのエリアが…
What Princess Euphemia
did was clearly a failure.
If we deal with this incorrectly,
this may spread to every Area!
殿下！　今はコーネリア皇女殿下を
My Lord!
We must help Princess Cornelia!
兄上 私が行きましょう
Brother, why don't I go there?
そ… そうか？　行ってくれるか
Y- You will?! You'll go there?!
悲しいじゃないですか
人が殺し合うのは…
Don't you find it sad to see
those people killing each other?
超電磁式留散弾重砲
Superconducting heavy
shrapnel cannon, FIRE!
発射！
CHARGING
FIRE
Special Unit 1, move in!
第一特務隊！　突っ込めー！
The Britannians seem to only be
defending the government bureau.
ブリタニアは政庁だけ 守るつもりだな
They're avoiding scattering their forces and
waiting for reinforcements, just as I expected!
武力の拡散を避け 援軍を待つ
やはりそうきたか
Freeze! We're the Black Knights!
We've occupied this building!
動くな！　黒の騎士団だ！
ここは我々が占拠した！
指示に従ってもらおう
You will do as we tell you to!
そ そんなあ… あっ まさか…
No... It can't be!
さあ 世界中に
発信しようじゃないか ゼロを
Now then, shall we
transmit this to the world?
世の中が変わる瞬間を
The moment that Zero
changes everything, Chief?
部長
はっ はい
R- Right!
大衆が望む最高の画が撮れそうですよ
We're going to give the public
the greatest show they ever hoped to see!
ん…
これで… 全部の放送局が…
That makes it every
broadcasting station!
あっ！
手を上げて後ろを向け！
Hands up and turn around!
この学校は
俺達 黒の騎士団がもらった！
The Black Knights have now taken this school!
銃を下ろせ！
Lower the guns!
はあん？　何言ってんだ この状況で
Huh? That's a hell of a thing
to say in this situation!
クー
リヴァル
Rivalz!
Lemme be cool for once!
I'm protecting everyone here!
ここは かっこつけさせてくれよ
俺がみんなを守る
ああ そうかい！
Oh, is that a fact?!
うっ！
やめろ！
Stop!
えっ
あっ
ああ…
手荒な真似はするなと言ったはずだ
I told you to avoid violence!
But, you told us this was gonna
be our command center!
で… でもよ
ここに司令部をおくって言うから
司令部って…
Command center?!
何も アッシュフォードじゃなくても…
Why does it have to be
Ashford, of all places?!
この学園は 我々 黒の騎士団が徴用し
司令部として使用させてもらう
This academy is of great use to us Black Knights,
so we're using it as our command center.
拒否権は ないのよね？
We can't refuse, can we?
君達の身の安全は保証しよう
I guarantee
you will be unharmed.
ナナリー 戦いが終わるまで
ここは黒の騎士団に守らせる
Nunnally, until the fighting is over,
the Black Knights will protect you here. So, please...
だから…
そんなの信じられるかよ！
戦争してんだろ？　俺達ブリタニアと！
Like we can believe you?!
You guys are at war with us Britannians!
リヴァル　お願い　言う通りにして
Rivalz, please.
Do what he says.
あっ！　カレン？
Kallen!
I see. So, that's how it is...
Do I have your word?
そっか… そういう事か
約束してくれる？
あたし達だけじゃなく
学園の生徒 全員に手を出さないって
Not just us! Tell me you won't harm
any of the students on campus!
男子寮も女子寮も
If nobody leaves the boys or girls dorms,
they should be fine.
外には出られないようにしたから
大丈夫だと思う
ねえ 私に何をしたの？
Tell me, what did you do to me?
えっ
私がどれだけ怖かったか…
You don't know how scared I was.
２人でやったんでしょ？
私に… 何か…
You both did something
to me, didn't you?!
Huh?
はあ？
How could you?
How could you?!
ひどいよ　ひどい！
ゼロ！　ランスロットが！
Zero, it's Lancelot!
やはり来たか！
I knew he'd come!
CODE GEASS
Lelouch of the Rebellion
どけえー！
Out of my way!
うわあー！
Where is Zero?! I'LL KILL HIM!!!
ゼロはどこだ？　俺はゼロをー！
ギアス？
Geass?
そう ゼロは超常の力を持っている
Correct. Zero possesses
a supernatural power.
まさか…
Impossible.
ユーフェミア皇女殿下は
なぜ急に人が変わった？
Then why did Princess Euphemia
suddenly change so completely?
そして
And what about you,
the one who always follows the rules?
ルールを遵守しようとした君は
式根島で何をした？
What about what you did
on Shikine Island? In short...
つまり…
人を操り 記憶を失わせる力…
The power to control people
and erase their memory!
そう考えれば今までの事も
全て つじつまが合う
When you think about it, it coherently
explains everything that's happened till now.
恐らく その後遺症で私は
イレヴンなどと
And in its aftereffects,
I fell in love with a damned Eleven!
あの学生
ルルーシュ・ランペルージこそ諸悪の
That student... Lelouch Lamperouge!
He's guilty of all of it!
Suzaku!
スザク！
カレンか？
Kallen?!
戦場で会った以上
悪いけど ここで死んでもらう
We meet in battle again.
I'm sorry, but this time
you're going to die!
みんなバカだ！　君も日本人も
あんな男に騙されて！
You're all fools! You, the Japanese,
everyone being tricked by that man!
その言い方ムカツクね！
あんたにゼロの何が分かるって言うの！
I can't stand that kind of talk!
What do you even know about Zero?!
じゃあ教えてくれ！　ゼロを！
Then tell me what you know about him!
ゼロは今どこにいる！
TELL ME WHERE ZERO IS NOW!
いっ…
くうっ
さあ 答えろ！　ゼロはどこだ！
Come on, answer me!
Where is Zero?!
I won't tell a traitor like you!
言うはず ないだろ！　裏切り者がー！
じゃあ ここで終わりにする！
Then let's finish this here!
飛べるからって調子に乗るな！
Don't get so full of yourself,
just because you can fly!
うっ！
うっ
捕まえた！
I've got you!
くらいなあっ！
EAT THIS!
うわあー！
さあ 言え！　ゼロはどこだ！
Now tell me! Where is Zero!
I hate pushy guys, you know.
しつこい男は嫌いなんだけど
そうか ならここで…
I see. Then die here.
くっ
何か言い残す事は ないかい？
Any last words?
Wait!
待て！
う…
え？
枢木スザク 君に対する執着が
私の甘さだったようだ
Suzaku Kururugi, it seems I was naive
to try and convince you to join me.
断ち切る為にも
一騎打ちにて決着をつけたいのだが
Would you like to settle this
one-on-one to make up for my mistake?
望むところだ！
Fine with me!
Tohdoh!
藤堂さん
朝比奈か
Asahina. What about Urabe?
卜部の方は？
予定通り
エナジーフィラーの保管所を押さえました
Moving in on the energy filler
depository, right on schedule.
よし 仙波と千葉も合流させろ
Okay, then let's rendezvous
with Senba and Chiba.
補給完了後 政庁を包囲
我が本体は正面から押し出す！
Once we recharge,
we'll surround the government bureau.
Then we in the main force
will push in from the front!
承知！
Wilco!
Order Lord Crane to fall back.
クレイン卿には後退を指示
駅構内に防衛線を敷かせろ
Set up a defense line
on the railway station grounds.
イエス ユア・ハイネス
Yes, Your Highness.
コーネリア殿下
Princess Cornelia, I've reached our encampment.
What about the bureau's defense line?
陣を敷き終えました
政庁前の防衛線は？
Hold your position.
そのまま維持しろ　この戦が長引けば
黒の騎士団の方が不利になる
If we drag this battle out,
it'll be bad for the Black Knights.
イエス ユア・ハイネス
Yes, Your Highness.
で 兄上の方は なんと？
Well, what does my
older brother say?
75時間後に 太平洋の艦隊が到着すると
He says the Pacific fleet
should arrive in 75 hours.
エリア11内では サドとトリシマの
航空部隊が既に出ています
Also, within Area 11, the Sado and Torishima
air divisions have already been deployed.
という事は あと30分ほどか
その情報を黒の騎士団にリークしろ
Meaning they should
be here in about 30 minutes.
Leak that information
to the Black Knights!
えっ！
リーク後 お前達はギルフォードと共に
政庁正面を守り抜け
After the leak, you will defend the
bureau's front line with Lord Guilford.
And you, Princess Cornelia?
コーネリア殿下は？
宴の準備だよ
I'll be preparing the party.
ゼロぉぉー！
ZERO-O-O-O!!!
Can't you calm him down?!
まだ落ち着かんのか！
His resistance is too strong!
抵抗が大きすぎて…
コーネットピンを取り付けます
We've mounted the radiator fins!
うっ う…
Ｔ４が政庁方向に？
T4's headed for the government bureau?
敵の航空部隊がもう着いたのか？
Are the enemy air divisions
here already?
いや　１機だけらしい
No, just one unit so far.
なら体制に影響は ないだろう
Then it shouldn't affect
too many of us.
学園地区は我々が
We're holding the school and Diethard's
group are holding the media areas.
メディア地区はディートハルト達が押さえ
Lady Kaguya is standing by
on the rear line.
後詰めとして神楽耶様もいる
あとは後方さえ押さえれば勝てる
All we need is to push in
on their rear line and we've won.
死んでいった吉田達の為にも…
We need to, for Yoshida
and the others who died.
副指令 不審者を捕らえました
Sub-commander,
we've captured a stranger.
学生か？　なら逃がしてやれ
監禁する理由など ないのだから
A student? Then let them go.
We have no reason to hold them.
いえ 裏門から校内に
侵入しようとしたところを…
No, they were caught sneaking
in through the rear gate.
侵入？
Sneaking in?
あっ！
千草…
Chigusa!
か… 彼女は直属の協力員だ
別室に案内を
Sh- She's a collaborator
who reports directly to me.
Take us to another classroom.
I'll hear her report directly there.
俺が直接 報告を聞こう
ニーナ　まだガニメデの倉庫に
いるのかしら？
Nina's still in the
Ganymede hangar.
それより カレンでしょ
And Kallen's part of this?
Oh... What are we going to do?
あー どうなるんだろ？　俺達
大丈夫よ
It's all right.
あ？
黒の騎士団は…
The Black Knights...
Or rather, Zero...
いえ ゼロは…
絶対に私達に危害を加えないから
They absolutely won't do
anything to harm us.
なんで言い切れるんだよ
Why are you so sure?
Coward!
卑怯者！
いっ！
あ！
あ…
え？
人質のつもりか　何が一騎打ちだ
You've taken hostages?!
Some one-on-one fight this is!
That's entirely your own fault
for rejecting my offers to join us!
仲間になる機会を
ことごとく裏切ったのはお前だ
くだらん美学に
こだわった事を悔いるがいい
Now, regret this ridiculous set
of aesthetics you cling to!
おい　あの黒いナイトメア
ニュースで出ていた奴だろ？
Hey, that black Knightmare's
the one that was on the news, right?
そんな… ゼロがここを狙うなんて…
It can't be... Zero's targeting
this building?! He can't be!
嘘よ！
嘘！　だって そんな事したら…
He can't! Because, if he does!
く… 懐に入ってハーケンを…
If I can get at his chest and use the Harkens...
ZERO!!!
ゼロー！
ゴー！
Go!
Wha?! Why, you!
うっ　これは！
うふふ…
やっぱり これの対策を
とっている時間は なかったようね
I figured they didn't have time to come
up with a countermeasure for this.
Zero, as promised.
ゼロ　約束通り
ああ その機体は好きにしろ
Yes. You can do with
the machine as you wish.
Zero! You trick people to
the very end! You betray them!
ゼロ！　お前は最後まで人を騙して
裏切って！
ふん　偽善なる遊びに付き合う暇はない
I have no time to argue
who's the bigger hypocrite here.
さらばだ　枢木スザク
Farewell, Suzaku Kururugi.
くそー！
DAMMIT ALL!
さすがに守りは堅いな
Their defenses
are as stiff as expected.
Should you really be
so laid back about this?
呑気に構えている場合か？
敵の援軍がご到着だ
Enemy reinforcements are arriving.
If they start bombing us, it's all over.
爆撃されたら おしまいだな
ふん
エナジーフィラーは交換済みだろ？
Our energy filler's been
replenished, hasn't it?
藤堂 私は政庁の上から攻め込む
Tohdoh, I'm going to move
in on the bureau from above.
Hm? Isn't it risky to rely on
the abilities of that machine?
ん？
機体能力に頼るのは危険だと考えるが
分かっている　混乱を作るだけだ
I understand.
I'm just going to cause some confusion.
It looks like...
似ているな
ああ アリエスの離宮に
Yes. Aries Villa.
なぜ知っている？
How do you know that?!
話してやるよ　いずれ…
その時が来たらな
I'll tell you some day,
when the time comes.
ん…
Welcome, Zero.
ようこそ　ゼロ
んっ
やはり空爆情報に誘い出されて
ここに来たな
I figured you'd come here
if you knew about the air raid.
Now, come to your welcome party!
さあ 歓迎の宴だ
舞踏会は お好きかな？
Do you fancy a dance?
千草 どうしてこんな戦場に来たんだ？
Chigusa, why did you
come to this battlefield?!
安全な所を探すから ひとまず俺と…
We need to find you someplace safe.
For now, stay with me...
あっ
あ…
その… 隠していて悪かった
Look... I'm sorry
I hid this from you.
でも これは平和の為に
やっている事なんだ
But I'm doing this
for the sake of peace!
ゼロがブリタニアから日本を解放すれば
俺達は一緒になれる
If Zero can free Japan from Britannia,
we can be together!
気持ち悪い事を言うな！
Oh, stop before I puke!
んっ
私とお前みたいなイレヴンが一緒になる
I and an Eleven like you, together?
ふっ 私の名はヴィレッタ・ヌゥ
ブリタニアの騎士候だ
My name is Villetta Nu,
Knight of Honor of Britannia!
あっ あの…
B- But...
あ… あ…
そ… そうか
So, Chigusa...
You got your memory back...
千草 記憶が戻っ… たのか… あ…
扇が撃たれたって？
Ohgi's been shot?!
はい　今 医療班が診ています
Yeah. The medic's
taking care of him now.
撃ったのは あの女か？
And it was the woman
who shot him?!
確かな事はまだ… 捜索はしています
We're still not sure.
We're searching for her now!
待て！
Wait!
え？
扇の事は これ以上広めるな
みんな動揺する
Don't tell anyone else about Ohgi.
It'll just shake them up.
女だけ捜すんだ
Just find the girl!
分かりました
Gotcha!
Oh... Now they've even got Suzaku!
ああ… このままじゃスザクまで
あ！
Something must have happened.
何かあったのかしら？
今のうちです　行って下さい
Now's your chance. Please, go!
えっ？
スザクさんを 助けてあげて下さい
ここで今 一番頼りになるのは…
Please, go help Suzaku!
He's our best hope here!
うん
こんな所に犯人が隠れていたら
分からないな
You'd never know if the
culprit was hiding in here.
Where's the light switch?
照明の電源は？
Dunno.
さあ？
いっ
あー
あっ あっ…
ゼロ！　ユーフェミア様の…
Zero... Princess Euphemia...
WILL BE AVENGED!!!
仇ー！
What's wrong, Zero?!
どうした ゼロ！
スペックでは圧倒しているはずなのに！
I thought the specs on this
thing were overwhelming!
Weakling!
ぜい弱者があ！
捕まえた！
I have you!
Your life is now in my hands!
お前の命は今 まさに私の手の中に！
Cornelia!
コーネリア！
これが裁きだ！
This is your judgment!
うあっ！
Princess, it's me, Darlton.
姫様　ダールトンです
あ…
Wha? But, why?
なぜだ…？
ご安心を… お命までは頂きません
Have no fear.
I will not kill you.
間に合ったか
He made it.
ゼロに姫様を差し出す為に
I'm doing this to deliver you
to Zero, Your Highness.
はっ あ…
姫様…
Princess! Why?!
なぜ…
Thank you, Darlton.
ありがとう　ダールトン
PRINCESS!!!
姫様ー！
あ…
あら？　もしかしてC.C.さん？
Hm? Is that you, C.C.?
違うよ
No.
え？　でも…
Hm? But...
ナナリー 君を迎えに来たんだ
Nunnally...
I've come for you.
モザイクカケラ ひとつひとつ
Mosaic kakera
The pieces of a mosaic
Hitotsu hitotsu tsunagiawasete
Coming together one by one
繋ぎ合わせて描いてゆく
Egaiteyuku
To form the picture
あなたがくれた 出逢いと別れも
Anata ga kureta deai to wakare mo
The meetings and partings I've had with you
こんなはずじゃない そう思って眠り
Konna hazu ja nai
"It can't be," I think
Sou omotte nemuri
As I go to sleep
目覚めればいつもの 変わらない空回り
Mezamereba itsumo no
When I awaken, just as always
Kawaranai karamawari
I'm left going nowhere
意味も無く繰り返し
Imi mo naku kurikaeshi
Pointlessly repeating the pattern
モザイクカケラ 鮮やかに映す
Mosaic kakera
The pieces of a mosaic
Azayaka ni utsusu
Clearly showing
過去の嘘も過ちも
Kako no uso mo ayamachi mo
The lies and mistakes of the past
消してしまいたいと想えば想うほど
Keshiteshimaitai to omoeba omou hodo
As much as I'd like to erase them
振り返れば
Furikaereba soko ni aru
When I look back, I see...
そこにあるスタートライン
Start line mada susun ja inai
I still haven't moved past that start line
未だ進んじゃいない
もう一度夢を拾い集めてみよう
Mou ichido yume wo
So let's try regathering
Hiroiatsumete miyou
the pieces of our dream
モザイクカケラ ひとつひとつ
Mosaic kakera
The pieces of a mosaic
Hitotsu hitotsu tsunagiawasete
Coming together one by one
繋ぎ合わせて描いてゆく
Egaiteyuku
To form the picture
あなたがくれた 出逢いと別れも
Anata ga kureta deai to wakare mo
The meetings and partings I've had with you
第二皇女コーネリアは 我が手に落ちた
Cornelia, the second princess of the empire,
has fallen into my hands.
あとは母を殺した犯人を暴き
人質とすれば俺の勝ちだ
After I ask her who killed my mother,
I just have to hold her
hostage and I've won.
そして ナナリーの為にも
And then,
for Nunnally's sake as well,
完膚なきまでにブリタニアを叩き潰す
I'll bring all of Britannia to its knees!
俺達を捨てた あの国を！
The country which
abandoned us both!
ZERO